https://lamatek.com/privacy

PhoneEmailFacebookInstagramLinkedinTwitterYoutube
© LAMATEK, Inc. | www.lamatek.com | 1-800-LAMATEK (local 856-599-6000)
LAMATEK is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our content, products and services. We want to provide a safe and secure environment for you and your children. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct this information. Our policy allows you to choose what kind and how much information you provide to us and to control how we use whatever information you give us. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have. This policy applies only to LAMATEK and not to other companies’ or organizations’ websites to which LAMATEK is linked.
Collection of information
Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or not.
LAMATEK collects two types of information. The first type is anonymous information. For instance, we may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth – they are ‘anonymous’ to us. This information is collected for research purposes, is used in the aggregate (where possible), and remains anonymous. The second type of information that LAMATEK collects is personal information. LAMATEK will collect personal information that lets us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address, or postal address, when you provide it to us. With this information, LAMATEK can provide a variety of personalized and enhanced services that are not available to anonymous users. We hope that you will find it beneficial to provide individually identifiable information about yourself to us because it will make our services more valuable to you.
Sometimes, we may specifically ask for personal information about you when you sign up to use a service. Certain information may be required, such as your name, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number, etc. in order to provide that service or product to you. This information may also be used to inform you of additional products and services which may interest you. You can choose not to receive such information when you are undertaking product or service registration on our website. We may also ask about your interests, but it is your choice whether to respond.
How much of your personal information that you choose to disclose to LAMATEK is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us.
Use of anonymous information
LAMATEK automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of lamatek.com like the numbers and frequency of visitors to lamatek.com and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve lamatek.com to assure that it is as appealing to as many users as possible. LAMATEK.com may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.
Use of personal information
LAMATEK will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. LAMATEK will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.
Cookies
Lamatek.com currently uses cookies. These cookies are used strictly for the purposes of identifying your requests as belonging to you. These cookies delete themselves automatically in 20 minutes, therefore if youâ€™re on our site for more than 20 consecutive minutes, you may be required to log back in.
LAMATEK uses Google Adwords tracking cookies for remarketing. This means you may see ads from us on other websites that are part of the Google Content Network (GCN). This allows us to continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service. As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing system. You may opt out of this technology at any time by using Google’s opt out feature.
Disclosure
There will be occasions where it will be necessary for us to disclose your personal information to third parties. We may be required by law to disclose the information, or we may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested. For example, if you purchase products online from LAMATEK, we will need to disclose your personal information to third parties in order to bill and deliver your products. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organization or person outside of LAMATEK unless you have authorized us to do so.
No sale of personal information
Under no circumstances will LAMATEK sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.
Access and correction: personal data
If LAMATEK holds your personal information we will provide you with access to the information, where possible. Reasonable steps will be taken to correct your information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.
Complaints about privacy
If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on our websites, please notify LAMATEK. While we accept no liability for any material or links posted to the service, we will investigate all complaints.
Changes to LAMATEK privacy policy
If we decide to change the LAMATEK Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.
©
2020 LAMATEK, Inc. All rights reserved.1226 Forest Parkway • West Deptford, NJ 08066 • 1-800-LAMATEK
About Us
Company Profile
LAMATEK’s Timeline
Customer Reviews
Upcoming Events
Careers & Employment
Community Involvement
Information & Policies
Medical Products
Personal Protective Equipment (PPE)
HVAC(R)
Air Filter Gasketing
Duct Gaskets
Flange Gaskets
Damper Gaskets
Foam Sealant Tape
Roof Curb Tape
Foam Filters
Sheet Metal Bonding Tape
Back To Top
Our website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out.ACCEPT - I love cookies.I do not accept.Review Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Get a Price Quote for PROTEK Surface Protection Film
X
